Summary

Lead Technician with experience in Windows, Linux, networking and more. Worked in a warehouse environment as well as an office environment. Also have QA experience in both desktop and web-based environments.

Skills

- VirtualBox
- Software system testing
- Test case development
- Documentation
- HTMI

JIRA

https://www.linkedin.com/in/neil-goswami | Skynetuser127001.github.io/

- VMware
- Microsoft PowerShell
- Python
- Azure DevOps
- SmartSheet
 Management
- Microsoft Excel

Experience

Orange County Supervisor of Elections | Orlando, FL

05/2022 - 11/2022

Lead IT Technician (Contract)

10/2023 - present

- Delivered on-the-job training and development initiatives to new field technicians.
- Tested proprietary DS200 and DS300 voting machines and reported any issues faced during testing.
- Created local area networks for ballot printers to communicate with tablets.
- Disassembled and reassembled Logitech and Oki Ballot printers.
- Created a new updated build for voting software on tablets.
- Maintained strict supervision on printers, tablets, and voting machines on Early Voting to successfully prevent tampering.
- Formatted Proprietary USB Drives that hold Election data for previous elections that have been stored in records.
- Printed signs and laminated them for events (ex. Swearing in of new Supervisor of Elections)
- Printed Ballots used for elections held in Orange County schools.
- Visited different precincts on election day during municipal elections to assist with technical issues.
- Used management software to keep inventory of every voting machine and tablet being sent out to precinct locations and early voting sites.

Central Florida Expressway Authority | Orlando, Florida

08/2021 - 12/2021

Quality Assurance Analyst (Contract)

- Conducted different types of testing methods on the website, CRM, and mobile application for toll collector, Epass.
- Generated reports of successful tests in Microsoft Excel.
- Opened tickets in Jira ticketing software whenever an issue is found and informed the Developers.
- Conducted regression and negative testing
- Worked with developers to fix security vulnerabilities and improve the security of software applications.
- Successfully identified and reported over 100 security vulnerabilities in software applications.

Education and Training Certifications

B.S.: Information Technology, Florida International University 2021

Relevant Courses: Data Structures, Computer Networking

- CompTia Certification Network+
- Kaseya Certification IT Automation
- Adobe Certified Associate Web Authoring Using Adobe Dreamweaver
- Adobe Certified Associate Visual Communication Using Adobe Photoshop